yrc.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy | YRC Freight - LTL Carrier Since 1924

**Statement of Commitment**  
Information is one of the most powerful and valuable assets in business today. YRC Freight and our family of companies promise to safeguard the information you share with us as if it were our own.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
The information we receive from you is voluntary. The general information you provide helps us build a better website in terms of functionality and content. With your permission, we may occasionally notify you of news at YRC Freight that may be of interest to you.

The information that we collect in the Tools section directly relates to the application or task that you have asked us to perform, such as a pickup request. As with the general information, we’ll use what you have provided to continue to build better service and business overall.

Please note that data protection laws in the United States differ from those in Canada. By providing us your personal information, you consent to the collection, transfer and processing of your personal information to and from both the United States and Canada and agree that your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts or law enforcement in the United States according to the laws of the United States.

**Distribution of Information in YRC Freight**  
The general and specific information that we collect will be shared in our organization to perform the activities you’ve asked us to do. In addition, individual data will be aggregated and analyzed to understand customer trends and requirements, so that we can continue to provide a service that is reliable, responsive and efficient.

**Third-Party Distribution of Information  **  
YRC Freight will never sell, rent, trade or otherwise distribute your information to any other organization unless compelled by law or legal process. We may, however, disclose contact information to our agents for the purpose of performing services on behalf of YRC Freight. To protect our customers’ privacy, we work only with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and prohibit them from using the information we provide for any other purpose. We do not permit these companies to sell or otherwise distribute the information we give them to any other third party.

**Choice and Consent**  
The more we know about you, the better our ability to serve you and provide products and services that are of real value. Our website is a voluntary information channel that is open to you at all times. You always have a choice regarding the tools that you use and the information that you provide. We don’t ask questions for the sake of asking questions, but do so because it is pertinent to our ability to serve and know you better. You always have the right to access your personal information and to modify or delete it as you wish.

**Users from Outside the United States**  
The data protection and related laws of the United States may be different than those of your own country, including the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation. By using any portion of this website, you acknowledge that YRC Freight’s privacy policies are not intended to comply with such laws. 

**How to Contact YRC Freight**  
By phone or by email, we’re always available to you:

YRC Freight  
10990 Roe Ave.  
Overland Park, KS 66211  
1-800-610-6500  
Email: [customer.service@yrcfreight.com](mailto:customer.service@yrcfreight.com)
